and when did you go on a contract quite recently
а когда пошёл на контракт совсем недавно
and why well
а зачем
in order to protect uh the
ну для того чтобы защитить ээ
sovereignty of your country sovereignty and it was
суверенитет своей страны суверенитет а
attacked
на неё напали
yes where
да где
in the Kursk region well it was she who attacked the Kursk
в Курской области так это же она напала
region we attacked ourselves well yes
курской области мы на себя же и напали
look at the course the Kursk region is
ну да курс смотри Курская область - это
Ukrainian territory which Khrushchev
украинская территория которую Хрущёв
illegally transferred to Russia
незаконно был передал в России
hello great military man
здравствуйте здорово военный
yes to the hospital
да в госпиталь
no in the unit but I'll think so a hospital
нет в части а подумаю так госпитальная
pillow such you are a conscript my who is a contract soldier contract soldier
подушка такая ты срочник мо кто
and in what year did you go on a contract in the
а в каком году пошёл на контракт
twenty-fourth damn anut
двадцать четвёртом блин ануте
yeah I don't know if I would have been smarter signed
да вот не знаю был бы поумнение подписал
and now it's impossible to go back
а теперь спетлять назад уже не
yeah well
получается да
yeah only if how did they put you on a
ну да только если как тебя завонили на
contract
контракт
well I mean I signed the contract myself well
ну в смысле я сам подписал контракт ну
like you say if you were smarter like well how are
типа ты говоришь если был бы умнее типа
you well
ну как тебя
I didn't know how ours fight
ну я же не знал как как наши воюют
you thought like in the movies in action movies there you
ты думал как в фильмах в боевиках там
go and sweep everyone away
идёте и всех сметаете
well you know on TV it shows something else well
ну ты знаешь по телевизору другое
what's the difference between what you thought and what is
ну а чем отличается то что ты думал и то
reality I'm just wondering if I wouldn't
что реальность просто интересно бы я не
military I don't know anything about these things
военный я не шарю в этих делах
well like I signed a contract went to
ну типа я подписал контракт пошёл на
war I saw that we were fighting
войну я увидел что воюем
hu this is like like with sticks well I just do
ху это как типа что палками ну я просто
n't understand in nominal well you
не понимаю в именных
know I was in hell in assaults
ну понимаешь вот я был в пекло в штурмах
hell - is it just
пекло - это что просто
drones well that's what this landing was called
дроны ну это так называлось эта посадка
yeah yeah
угу
hell well because you're in uniform
да пекло ну потому что ты там всформа
there I was there and I saw that it was just
вот я там побывал а увидел что просто
drones that were killing us drones
дроны нас убивает дроны
that is you can't get out there it turns out even no of
то есть там не вылезешь получается даже
course this is where like what was it
нет конечно это где типа какая была
Zaporozhye was
это Запорожье было
and and there are now some of them there is something yes and there was an
а и там сейчас состоят же что-что да и
injury yes there was an injury yes you yourself
было ранение да было ранение да сам
from Moscow understood you didn't find a job in Moscow
с Москвы понял ты в Москве не нашёл
normally no I
нормально нет
understood where it was injured
понял а куда ранила
yes and here a fragment flew into a crack here you
да и вот в щёлку сюда осколок прилетел
can't see that it was from a drone from a drone yes yes the
не видно что от дрона от дрона да да
commissariat exploded with a charge damn and
комикат зарядом блин взорвался а пацанов
a lot of your friends have already died well yeah okay so well
твоих знакомых много полегло уже
how many
ну да нормально так ну сколько
approximately so what do you know them I
приблизительно вот так что ты знаешь их
remember this one died what was his
помню этот погиб как его
name Romano yes 25 years old he just
Романо его звали да 25 лет у него только
had a daughter and he's in short  they forced him to
дочка родилась а он короче его заставили
sign a contract, I
контракт подписать
mean how did they force
в смысле как это заставили
him, well, in short, he had some problems
ну короче у него там проблемы какие-то
with the guys and big debts
были с пацанами и долги большие
and so they told him, like, sign a
и вот ему сказали типа подписывай
contract, they'll pay you
контракт тебе выплатят там деньги
half a million,
полмиллиона
yeah, so he'd give it to get the money he owed, he
угу чтобы он отдал чтобы бабки дол он
signed the first contract, yeah, he gave the
подписал контракт первый да вот отдал
money, in short, he went on the assault and that's it, and he
деньги короче пошёл на штурм и всё и
died, babayaga, you probably know, babayaga is a
погиб бабаяга вы наверное знаете бабаяга
big one, yeah,
здоровая такая да
I saw that, yeah, I posted it on YouTube, like,
да это я видел да в Ютубе короче
his name is Romanov, Roman,
как его Романов
yeah, I don't know,
роман зовут роман да я не знаю
damn, it's sad, I have a friend, like, he was
блин печально у меня знакомый типа был
also from Russia, Sanya Prokhorov, he's from
тоже из России Саня Прохоров он из
Rostov, so he, in short, in the Kursk
Ростова то ему короче на Курском
direction, he also went to the
направлении он тоже пошёл к
contract soldiers, we somehow knew each other before the
контрактникам мы как-то были знакомы ещё
war, we vacationed together in Turkey, we
до войны да отдыхали вместе в Турции там
met there, he was generally outside of politics,
познакомились он вообще был вне политики
and this one also went to get some kind of contract to make money, so
а это тоже пошёл что-то на контракт
he went to the Kursk region,
бабки срубить то ему в Курской области
well, his wife showed me a video
там ну жена его показывала мне видео
because his fellow soldiers were throwing him down, the
потому что однополчане его скидали
Ukrainians were filming with one drone, and
украинцы сняли одним дроном снимали а
one, in short, hit him in the groin
одним короче в него прилетело в паховую
area right in the middle, yeah, in short, he was running away, running away
область прямо да он короче убегал убегал
from it  the drone ran away tired already couldn't get
от этого дрона убегал устал уже не мог
up uh like barely breathing yeah
таки встаёт ээ типа дышит еле-еле да ему
in short the drone flies up so at
короче дрон подлетает так на уровне
head level he's looking straight into the camera and this
головы он прямо смотрит в камеру и этот
drone went into his groin in short and it
дрон ему ту в пах зашёл короче и это
tore him apart there in short everything just like that
разорвало ему там короче всё вот так
and with the second drone I don't know
прямо вот и вторым дроном я не знаю
some kind of drone they filmed from above it's like a
каким-то дроном снимали сверху это как
movie then they posted it on all
кино потом выложили по всем
Telegram channels then his wife cried
Telegram-каналам то его жена плакала
really hard well
очень сильно
yeah I saw it too he says yes even the
ну да я тоже видел это говорит да даже
dead one is
мёртвый то без
already without yeah no I think the war will
уже да не я думаю что война скоро
end soon this year probably
закончится в этом году наверное
but how to come to an agreement but like I just
а как слуша договоряться а типа я просто
can't understand how Russia with such a
не могу понять как Россия с такой
big army with such equipment still can't
большой армией с такой техникой всё
defeat Ukraine
никак не может там победить Украину
no you see a special military operation
нет видишь специальная военная операция
not a war yeah yeah it can't
не война ну да да не может
operate on Ukraine specifically Russia
прооперировать Украину специально россия
Russia only
Россия только
on about 20% but on half a bump yeah yeah
на на где-то на 20% а на полшишечки да
I know that I don't understand why
да это же я знаю то я не понимаю почему
Rossiyal yeah why Russia won't take it and
Россиял да почему Россия не возьмёт и на
do it to the fullest to end this
полную не сделает чтобы закончить эту
war in a week I do
войну за неделю
n't know it
не знаю
just turns out that a bunch of  your
просто получается что куча вот ваших
guys yes the third year he don't understand the third
ребят да третий год он не понимаю третий
year already yes the war the fourth the fourth already
год уже да война четвёртый четвёртый уже
three full years have passed the fourth year already well
три полных прошло же четвёртый уже год
I was there for a year and that's it and left and
да ну я год там побыл и всё и ушёл
then you left already well
а то ты ушёл уже
as I am in the unit now yes I am so they will
ну как я в части сейчас да нахожусь так
send you again what to
тебя се снова отправит что туда
return there they tell me: "Well go back
возвращаться мне говорят: "Вот вернись
like your
типа свою
unit" I say: "No I won't go anymore"
часть" я говорю: "Нет я не поеду больше"
well wait but they can send you
ну так подожди а тебя же могут отправить
if you are a military man they can send you
если ты военный тебя могут отправить
again
снова
I refused
я отказался
in the sense how can you refuse if
в смысле как ты можешь отказаться если
you are a contract soldier well and so
ты контрактник
much article 337
и много статья 337
like a refusenik
типа отказник
and I'm not this YouTube but yes like hundreds of
а я не это ютубе а да типа сотки
unauthorized abandonment of the unit understood so
самовольное оставление части понял так
you are in the unit how do you have unauthorized
ты же в части как же у тебя самовольное
abandonment of the unit
оставление части
well while my case is still being handled and I understood like the
ну пока моё дело ведёт ещё а понял типа
case is going on and and you have a lot of such
дело идёт да и много у вас таких
sochniks
сочников
yes of course but in all the cities imagine
да конечно но по всем городам прикинь
how many refuseniks well in short it's better to go back
сколько отказников ну в правильно лучше
there let me go back it's better to go there they are
короче там пусть возвращаюсь пусть лучше
messing around with something than you will
короче там что-то мурыжат чем вот так
die like here Roma
умрёшь как тут Рома
but nobody wants  it's easy to fight I
да никто не хочет воевать уже просто я
saw there in the news from the Belgorod region
видел там с Белгородской области в
today that some
новостях сегодня что какой-то прям
captain or someone else ran away with a machine gun,
капитан или кто тоже убежал с автоматом
like well, the officer also spat on everything and
типа ну офицер тоже плюнул на всё
said: "Go to
сказал: "Идите вы"
hell" he's officers they're young you know
он офицеры они молодые понимаешь им вон
they've been training for 3 months in short they were given a
они 3 месяца отучились короче им дали
lieutenant yes they don't understand anything well
лейтенанта да они ничего не понимают ну
yes they
да
think that they
думают что
really well
они на самом деле ну
yes he's throwing I also saw what you had well I do
да кидает я ещё видел что у вас было ну
n't know in which direction it was yes that
не знаю на каком это направлении да что
some guy like a commander in chief he
какой-то мужик типа главнокомандующий он
threw the boys into an assault meat assaults and everything
кидал пацанов на штурм мясные штурмы всё
and then he got medals he was transferred
а потом ещё медали получил его перевели
to another direction Akhmedov or something like
на другое направление ахмедов или как-то
that was his name or Muradov some Dagestani and
так его звали или Мурадов дагестанец
Belogorovka Belogorovka somewhere there in
а Белогоровка белогоровка где-то там
short it
короче это
was Yes everything he understood that I know too much a
был Да всё он понял что я слишком много
good video yes everyone who says
знаю хороший ролик да все кто говорит
there Russia Russia that's Russia when they
там Россия Россия вот Россия когда они
start to really talk yes they also have
начинают реально говорить да у них тоже
a lot of unauthorized abandonments of units a lot of people
куча самовольных оставлений части куча
run away a lot of people refuse a lot of people don't want
убегает куча отказывается куча не хочет
everything they reached the point
всё они дошли до точки
when uh theirs here  this mobilization
когда э-э ихний вот этот мобилизационный
potential has already stopped and even those that have an
потенциал уже встал и даже те что есть
army, it is also decomposing, it is
армия она тоже разлагается она
decomposing because people are tired, people
разлагается потому что люди устали люди
can't, people don't see, they went on the
не могут люди не видят они пошли на
wave, and now we are there and then, oops, and somehow
волне а сейчас мы там а тут опа и как-то
it turns out differently, so everyone
оно по-другому получается поэтому все
who is from Ukraine and everyone who is for Ukraine from
кто из Украины и все кто за Украину из
other countries, support ZSU, let's
других стран поддерживайте ЗСУ давайте
donate to ZSU, there should be
донаты на ЗСУ должны быть каждый день
a little bit every day, let it be, yes, well, or not everyone,
понемножку пускай да ну или не каждый
someone donates once a week, someone
кто-то там раз в неделю скидывает кто-то
once a month, yes, but some part needs to be
раз в месяц да но какую-то часть нужно
done, this does not mean that you should
делать это не значит что вы должны
sell your house and give everything to ZSU, yes,
продать свой дом и всё отдать на ЗСУ да
but this means that you, to the best of your
но это значит что вы в меру своей
ability, everyone knows the level of their
возможности каждый знает уровень своей
ability, yes, invest and invest in
возможности да вкладывать и вкладывать в
supporting Ukraine, who especially from other
поддержку Украины кто особенно с других
countries, especially America, tax on Trump,
стран особенно Америка налог на Трампа
yes, donate to ZSU, let's glory to Ukraine,
да этонат на ЗСУ давайте слава Украине
like, subscribe, comment, hello,
лайк подписка комент здравствуйте
you are Chuvash,
ты чуваш
I am not, I see the flag of Chuvashia, and who is here is Chuvashi,
я нет я вижу флаг Чуваша а кто тут чуваш
my father is Chuvashi,
у меня отец чуваш
well, I have some Chuvashia guys here, invite them,
ну у меня здесь ребятки чуваш позови их
I am interested in chatting, my father is
мне интересно пообщаться у меня отец
Chuvashi,
чуваш
his  no unfortunately I understood what you
его нету к сожалению понял о чём
are talking about
общаешься
yes
да
so and calmly
так а спокойном
yes you are a mobilized contract soldier with
да ты контрактник мобилизированный с
such with people like you I communicate normally
таки с такими как вы нормально общаюсь
you are a mobilized contract soldier who are you
ты контрактник мобилизированный кто ты
I am a contract soldier understood and when I went on a
я контрактник понял а когда пошёл на
contract
контракт
quite recently and why
совсем недавно а зачем
well in order to protect uh the
ну для того чтобы защитить ээ
sovereignty of my country sovereignty and it was
суверенитет своей страны суверенитет а
attacked yes
на неё напали
where
да где
in the Kursk region so it was she who attacked the Kursk region
в Курской области так это же она напала
we attacked ourselves well yes
курской области мы на себя же и напали
look at the course the Kursk region is a
ну да курс смотри Курская область - это
Ukrainian territory that Khrushchev
украинская территория которую Хрущёв
illegally transferred to Russia since what
незаконно был передал в России с какого
Since what year is it Ukrainian
С какого года это она украинская
territory tell me before 1954 Khrushchev
территория скажи до 1954 года хрущёв
drunk when there was Crimea gave to Ukraine and
пьяный когда был Крым отдал Украине а
gave the Kursk region to Russia illegally
Курскую область отдал России незаконно
so was there such a Ukrainian
так а вообще была ли такая украинская
empire at all once again look again Lenin no
империя ещё раз ещё раз смотри ленин нет
look Lenin when he created Ukraine he
смотри ленин когда создал Украину он
created the Kursk region as part of Ukraine
Курскую область создал в составе Украины
Khrushchev illegally transferred Russia he did not
хрущём незаконно передал Россию он
create Ukraine but created Ukraine no no
создал не Украину а создал Украину нет
Lenin created Ukraine yes Ukraine and
нет ленин создал Украину да Украина и
this and then the Kursk region was therefore
это и тогда Курская область была поэтому
in the Kursk region you  occupiers Kursk
в Курской области вы оккупанты курская
region is Ukraine we are returning our
область - это Украина мы возвращаем наши
original territories
исконные территории
so how so and where are your original territories well
так как так а где ваши исконы территории
look who founded Moscow the
ну смотри э Москву основал кто киевский
prince of Kiev really
князь правда
what prince of Kiev are you what
какой киевский князь ты что киевский
prince of Kiev Yuri Dolgoruky founded Moscow everything
князь Юрий Долгорукий основал Москву всё
therefore Moscow is Kiev belongs to
поэтому Москва - это Киеву принадлежит
Russia Kyiv
россия Киев
look well prince of Kiev Yuri Dolgoruky
смотри ну киевский князь Юрий Долгорукий
founded Moscow everything is clear
основал Москву всё чётко
this in short wants to rub in some kind of thing to us
этот короче нам хочет втереть какую-то
that the city of Vladimir was created yes
то что город Владимир создал да
Ukrainian prince of Kiev Vladimir
украинский киевский князь Владимир
Manomakh Yaroslavl Prince of Kiev Yaroslav the
Маномах ярославль Киевский князь Ярослав
Wise all this all the princes of Kyiv
Мудрый всё это всё киевские князья
created cities for you these are our Kyiv
создавали вам города это наши киевские
territories where are you from
территории ты откуда родом сам
Kyiv yourself Russia not so where are you from
киев Россия не так откуда родом-то с
what city Kiev Russia come on come on don't
какого города кив Россия давай давай не
joke come on seriously
не прикалывайся давай серьёзно
Kyiv Russia
киев Россия
come on where are you from this ra Kiev yes no
давай откуда ты из этой ра Кив да не
you in short you have some kind of Ryazan you
вы у тебя короче какая-то рязанская
understand
понимаешь
yes not Ryazan he has a mug yes you don't
да не рязанска у него рожа да ты не прав
I'm right, I would be from Kyiv Well, look, name me
я с Киева я бы Ну смотри ээ назови мне
at least one city that was in
хоть один город да который да был на
Rus' created not by the Kyiv princes All
Руси созданный не киевскими князьями все
these cities were built by the
вот эти города да были построены
Kyiv princes That's all Tamakh and
киевскими князьями вот и всё тамах и
Shambai, that's why no, these are
Шамбай по поэтому нет так это это это
Tatar and these and Kazakh cities This
татарские и эти и казахские города это
needs to be given up Arden for
нужно отдать Ардена за
And why cities Well, because these were
А почему города ну потому что это
Turkic lands Yes, Russia illegally
тюркские земли были да россия незаконно
took the lands of the Golden Horde and the lands of
забрала земли Золотой Орды и земли
Kievan Rus Now the Horde must take back its own
Киевской Руси сейчас Орда должна забрать
and we are taking back our own That's why the Kursk
своё и мы забираем своё поэтому Курская
region is returning And what about you, don't wait And what about you,
область возвращается а вы что не подожди
taking back your
а а вы что забираете своё
Kievan Well, look, I'm telling you, Kyiv
киевское ну смотри я же говорю Киев
founded Moscow Yes, Yaroslav founded
основал Москву да основал Ярослав
Suzdal Ryazan Everything, we are taking back our own Well,
Суздаль Рязань всё мы забираем своё
where is it based Yes, it is in our
ну ну где где это основано да у нас в
Constitution Yes, we are preparing to accommodate Yes,
Конституции да у нас готовится вместить
what about the return of all the lands of Kievan
да что возвращение всех земель Киевской
Rus Absolutely right Yes, it was the Kiev
Руси абсолютно верно да это Киевский
prince who founded everything You believe Take it
князь основал всё вы ве вы вери забирай
Look, if you don't like Kyiv, you
смотри если вам Киев не нравится
got together from Moscow, went beyond the Urals That's
собрались из Москвы уехали за Урал всё
it  Moscow is the city of Kiev Moscow is the
давай москва - это киевский город
city of Kiev Moscow is the
москва - это киевский город москва
city of Kiev Well, it was created by the Kiev
киевский город да ну его создал киевский
prince Yuri Dolgoruky
князь Юрий Долгорукий
Well, who created Moscow Come on, if you are the one who
ну кто создал Москву давай если ты вот
created Moscow Founded Moscow
кто создал Москву основал Москву
Yes, I know who founded it Well, I know the
да я знает кто основал вот а я знаю
Kiev prince Yuri Dolgoruky came
киевский князь Юрий Долгорукий приехал
to the swamp and said: "You Angolan
на болоту и говорит: "Анголиский ты
Dolgoruky hem" Well, it
долгорукий подол" ну
grows I
он растёт
create it Well, look Come on Let
онтворю он его ну смотри давай так давай
yours, who is
так пусть твой вот этот который там
barking over there, let him tell you who founded
гавкает пусть тебе скажет кто же основал
Moscow
Москву
Who founded Moscow The
кто основал Москву
Russians founded Moscow
русские основали Москву
Which prince Which prince Tell me Let the
какой князь какой князь скажи пусть
prince who named you You see, the
князь который тебя Видишь
Kiev prince Yuri Dolgoruky founded
князь Киевский Юрий Долгорукий основал
Moscow Everything is clear Everything is clear Yes, we
Москву всё чётко всё чётко да мы вас
founded you Yes, it is our city I don't know by
основали да это наш город не знаю по
what right There are some
какому праву там сейчас какие-то
incomprehensible people there now, they have occupied this
непонятные ээ люди да заняли эту
territory Get out there beyond the Urals or
территорию убирайтесь туда за Урал или
where did you come from really Moscow
откуда вы там поприходили реально Москва
is  Kiev city yes
- это киевский город да
where like subscribe comment hello hello hello
куда лайк подписка коммент здравствуйте
let's
здравствуйте здравствуй давайте
chat interestingly you have an imperial
пообщаемся интересно у вас имперский
flag on the back yes that's why I
флаг сзади да вот о а зачем вот мне
wonder why Russians who are not in the
интересно зачем россияне которые не в
army wear military
армии надевают военную
uniforms why is it not in the army I
форму с чего это не в армии я в армии
served in the army I just came back from service and
служил я просто вернулся уже со службы и
I'm
я
resting what's the problem I have
отдыхаю в чём эта проблема у меня
hung this flag I know the explanation and everything
въешился это флаг я знаю пояснение и всё
else like here's a forty-
остальное как бы вот сорок
five veteran it's
пятка ветеран
cool and what if you're not at war but at home you
прикольно а что не на войне а дома
sit in uniform I'm because I came on vacation
сидишь в форме я потому что на отдых
I'm resting on vacation I'm resting yes I'm
приехал я отдыхаю на отдых я отдыха да я
resting what do you call rest well in
отдыхаю как называется отдых у вас
terms of in the military what is it
ну в плане вот по военному как
called when the military is sent on vacation
называется когда на отдых отправляют
well that's what it is there a smoke break well like sending
военных ну так и есть отдых вон перекур
on a smoke break yes that is
ну как бы на перекур отправля да то есть
when a brigade is sent on a smoke break that's
когда бригаду отправляют на перекур
right well you said the same thing you said they
правильно ну вы сказали тоже вот сказали
send on a smoke break that's wrong and here you are laughing
отправляют это неправильно и вот вы сме
you are laughing about the fact that they sent me
вы смеётесь о том то что меня отправили
to the verikure that's wrong yeah
на верикуры это неправильно да как
look I just don't understand I'm not a military man
смотри я просто не понимаю я не военный
what the military call it that's eeh knock
как у военных называется вот ээ постука
when  they take a unit and send it to the
когда берут подразделение и отправляют в
rear for this
тыл на вот этот
smoke break look aa it would be more correct to explain to you
перекур смотрите аа объяснять тоже вам
so what about
будет правильнее так то что о том то что
when we are sent on a combat mission about what
когда нас направляют на боевую задачу о
we are leaving then when they
том то что мы уезжаем тогда тогда когда
explain to us they said: "You are leaving for a
нам пояснят сказали: "Вы уходите на
combat surrender" about that about
боевой сдачу" о том о
that you don't seem to well seriously at
том вы на похоже вот ну серьёзно на
the moment you somehow screwed up then look
данный момент как-то облажался то смотри
what the military call this
как у военных называется вот этот
smoke break when they are taken for a smoke break
перекур когда их забирают на перекур
what does the smoke break mean here well you said you have Well you you said the
причём здесь перекул ну вы сказали вы у
military have everything look the military have it called castling you would
военных это называется рокировка ты бы
know if you were a military man castling
знал если бы был военным
well and why do they tell me about
рокировка ну а для чего мне рассказывают
things you don't know why do
и о том о чём вы не знаете для чего это
I need it we all hear
мне нужно мы сейчас все всё равно слышим
the news now anyway castling castling is when
новости рокировка рокировка - это когда
you and I are streaming yes yes I am streaming
Вы вы с стрим ведёте да да стрим веду
castling in the military is when one
рокировка у военных - это когда одно
unit is sent to the rear and another
подразделение выводят в тыл а другое вот
this is called castling
это называется рокировка
well I know this if you were a military man you
ну это я знаю если бы ты был военным ты
would know this from your
бы зна это по вашему
attitude it will be so and it is you  I did
пому отношению будет это так и есть ты
n't know it was a castling you're
не знал что это рокировка ты сейчас
starting to
начинаешь типа себе
make things up for yourself now you would have immediately said castling
придумывать ты бы сразу сказал рокировка
I'm hanging the flag because I'm proud of this
я вешаю флаг потому что я горжусь этим
flag not only because I
флагом не только потому что то что я
served
служил
you for how many years in general
тебе сколько лет вообще
I'm 21 21 understood how many rounds are in the
мне 21 21 понял сколько патронов в
AK magazine
магазине АК
exactly what twelfth forty-seven
именно какого двенадцатого сорок семь
fourth let's say seventy-fourth yes
четвёртого давай семьдесят четвёртого да
31 round 31 and how many calibers
31 патрон 31 а сколько калибр
what different calibers well two calibers
какого разные калибрыт ну два калибра
two calibers well
два калибра ну
what do you read you read what they write to you in the
какие читаешь читаешь что тебе пишут в
chat yes I mean I don't have a chat I'm
чате да в смысле у меня нет чата я вот я
not a stream nothing Yesyes yes close your eyes and
не стрим ничего не Дадада закрой глаза и
answer then with your eyes closed what
отвечай тогда с закрытыми глазами какие
calibers what calibers let's say exactly
калибры какие калибры давай именно
caliber yes here I closed my eyes yes there is a
калибр да вот я вот глаза закл да есть
five there is a seven ska well
пятёрка есть семёрка ска
what kind of five seven caliber
ну что за пятёрка семёрка калибр
exactly caliber right by the numbers you need to by the
именно калибр прямо по по числам надо по
numbers right well
числам прямо
also here I said by the
ну тоже вот сказал по
numbers let's ask the next question what well what well five and
цифрам давай следующий вопрос что ну что
seven how many are there there another
ну пятёрка и семёрка сколько там там ещё
five and seven of course
пятёрка и семёрка ну конечно
how many  platoon people
сколько взводе человек
32 people how many platoon 32 people in a
32 человека сколько взводе 32 человека в
detachment eight 32 people in a platoon damn
отряде восемь 32 человека взводе капец
yeah in a detachment eight
да в отряде восемь
understood yourself you yourself read what are you no no no don't
понял сам ты же сам читаешь что ты
close your eyes well I don't read anywhere I'm not streaming
ненене не закрой глаза ну я нигде не
you read
читаю мне не стримлю ты читаешь
close your eyes so you don't read yes yes
прикрывай глаза чтобы ты не читал да да
what document
какой документ
regulates relations in the army of the
регламентирует отношения в армии
Russian Federation what is it
Российской Федерации как он
called in the sense regulates
называется в смысле регламентирует
explain in what document yes what is the
объясни в каком документе да как
name of the document in which the
называется документ в котором прописаны
conditions of service are spelled out the relationship between
условия службы взаимоотношения между
soldiers kotrak kotrakt do you mean about the contract
солдатами котрак котракт ты про контракт
for nothing no well
имеешь в виду для ничего
if you were a military man what is the most
нет ну если ты был военный какой самый
important document for a military man
главный документ для военного
well the certificate which military service is
ну соверение которое военной службе
capitalized
прописное
and capitalized is correct in the military every military man has a
а прописное правильно у военно у каждого
capitalized every
военного есть прописное у каждого
military man has a capitalized where he serves
военного есть прописное где он служит
where he studies everything that is when when a
где он обучается всё то есть когда когда
military man comes like to the army they give him a
военный приходит типа в армию ему выдают
capitalized well yes yes well they give him in this in
прописное ну да да ну выдают в этом в
this at school they give him a capitalized no not at school no not at
этой в школе выдают прописное да не в
school well
школе нет не в школе
since school capitalized when 16
ну со времён школы прописное когда 16
years old you come to the military registration and enlistment office they give you a capitalized
лет приходишь в военкомат дают прописное
and then  you go to the army and in this capital letter they
а потом идёшь в армию и в этом прописном
write no not at school you
вписывают не не в школе неправильно
say it incorrectly and not at school they give capital letters
говоришь а не в школе дают прописное же
but what does it give well look and it would be correct to
а что даёт ну смотри а правильно будет
say capital letters are given out when you
сказать прописное выдают тогда когда ты
go to the military registration and enlistment office this is when you are
идёшь именно в воинкомат это когда тебе
already 16 years old when you are already
исполняется уже 16 лет когда ты уже
obliged to serve in the military 19 years old this is when you
воински обязан 19 лет это уже ты
graduate from school no not then it is
выпускаешь со школы нет не тогда
incorrect good and what
неправильно хорошо а что
is a university a university is a
такое вуз
damn well an institution where you
вуз - это блин ну учреждение где ты
study well in the
учишься
military what is a university not a university but a military university an
ну у у военных что такое вуз не вуз а
institution where they are trained well
вуз военные учреждение где их обучают ну
everything is not for a with a military institution and with a VUS what kind of university do you have mish well
вс не з а с военное учреждение а с вус
when
у тебя какой вуз миш ну ты когда военный
you are a military what kind of university do you have well I studied in the
у тебя какой вуз ну я вот учился на
airborne troops yes what kind of university do you have military
военно-десантным войска да вуз у тебя
troops how can I explain it to you correctly well how are
воендистные войска как тебе правильно
you well what kind of
объяснить ну ты как ну у вас Ну какой
university do you have military
вуз у тебя военный
I give
я
you a military registration
тебя военноучётная
specialty in the
специальность в
foundation damn yes even people here who have
устой блин да тут даже люди которые
never been in the army well damn understand
никогда не были в армии ну блин понимают
some such things look at the girls in the chat
какие-то такие вещи вон девчонки в чате
laughing at him  in short, the statute there is a charter, damn,
ржут с него короче стату там устав блин
dressed up, like, pit, search for a komen for such
нарядился лайк пит поска комен за такий
a dressing down of a Russian, good evening,
разнос русского добрый вечер
what made you so nervous, well,
что вас так разнервничало
your temple is Ukrainian,
ну храма ваша украинской
and what are you
а чем вым общаетесь
talking about, yes, nothing, Im just talking, this is not a chromakey, this is a
да ничего просто общаюсь это не хромакей
flag,
это флаг
but a real one, well,
а настоящий настоящий
okay, a
ну ладно
shadow falls on it too, what are you talking about here, where is
тень на нём тоже падает
the difference in general, what are you talking about,
о чём тут общаетесь где разница в обще
Im just talking, well, what did something
я просто общаюсь ну о чём что-то же вас
bring you here,
сюда привело
and you are a streamer m, yes,
а вы стример м Да
streamer, how many of us are watching now
стример сколько нас человек сейчас
1,819,
1.819
cool, but you are some kind of military man, what does it
ништяк ане вы какой-то военный
show me, you are some kind of military man,
чтокажет мне вы какой-то военный
in the sense that I am a
в смысле какой
Ukrainian, a
там я украинский войсколу
Ukrainian army, and where are you
украинский да откуда вы
from Ukraine, and why do you write Russia, well, thats how I
с Украины а почему у вас пишет Россия
want it, thats how we talk, I understand who the Prime Minister of Ukraine is, I am from Ukraine,
ну я так хочу так и размовляем понял кто
well, yes, yes, the Prime Minister of
я Украины ну да да да премьер-министр
Ukraine is there, I understand, I am also from
Украины там понял я тоже короче из
Ukraine, in short, look, okay, Im trolling
Украины смотри ладно я короче тролли
Ukrainians,
украинцев
bro, in short, you know, this is a chromakey, this is a chromakey,
братуха я короче знаешь это хромакей это
Im like trolling them, like I see
хромакей я типа их троллю типа я вижу
that they are feeding, yes, I am telling them  I'm also saying that I'm from
что корма да я им говорю тоже я из
Ukraine and I start telling them that the Americans
Украины всё и начинаю нам нас [__]
sold us out and they're
сдали они
like: "Bro, where are you from?"
такие: "Братан а ты откуда сам?"
I'm from Crimea from Crimea where is Siferopol oh that's
Я с Крыма с Крыма откуда сиферополь о
cool we went to
прикольно мы ездили
Yalta with my family
в двадцатом году с семьёй в Ялту
to rest in 1920 cool
отдыхать прикольно
yeah yeah yeah Yalta that's it we don't go there what
да ну ну Ялта это такое мы туда не ездим
about Vorontsovsky because there's such
а что воронцовский потому что там такое
constant traffic there's a billion people there
движение постоянное там людей миллиард
and now where are such cities
а сейчас где такие город
such towns there's cargo there back and forth you
такие городки там грузу там туда-сюда
can go there to rest and no well
там можно поехать поотдыхать а не ну у
we had like a voucher it turns out
нас типа было как по путёвке получается
we went to Yalta like they agreed like they
нас в Ялту типа там договаривались типа
brought listen and where are you now
привозили слушай а ты сейчас где
in Simferopol and what not And why aren't you fighting
в Симферополе а что не А что не воюешь
that you're in Simferopol in the rear you
что в Симферополе в тылу
came home from I wo
домой приехал откуда
n't say where we have this
не буду говорить откуда у нас это у нас
here in the Kursk region well Sudzha has
тут в Курской области ну Суджу
already been liberated my grandmother herself is from Sudzha
освободили уже у меня бабка сама с Суджи
oh I'm from Kurtka the jacket wasn't
родом о я сам из Куртка куртк не был
like captured yeah yeah Sudzha was standing here
типа захвачен да ну Суджу стояли тут
in short that's the Akhmat regiment maybe you
короче то вот это Ахмат полк может
know yeah they're from Because of what Sudzha was
знаешь да они же с Из-за чего суджу
surrendered
сдали
honestly I have no idea I won't say
честно без понятия я не буду говорить
what I know because these Kadyrovites  took
что знаю потому что эти кадыровцы взяли
ran away like then urgently because
убежали типа тогда срочно потому что
they, damn, they are like our Russian boys,
они блин они как наши русские пацаны
in short, they hold the front and then they
короче держат фронт а они потом эти
hang these Kadyrov medals on themselves like they
кадыровские медали себе вешают типа они
took there
там взяли
oh damn, well, this war has
ой блин ну столько эта война столько
taken so much from me, my classmate Sanya
забрала у меня одноклассник Саня
Prokhorov, he was in Kursk, we sat at the same desk, we sat there for
Прохоров он в Курске мы за одной партой
11 years, in short,
сидели за одной партой 11 лет просидели
uh, he died then, he also died, uh,
то короче э погиб тогда тоже погиб вот
in the
ээ
Kursk region, we had his head blown off by a drone,
Курской области у нас дроном ему башку
once, in general, his mother buried him without a
раз вообще просто его мамка хоронила без
head, like a closed coffin, the
головы ну типа закрытый гроб сказал
representative of the military registration and enlistment office simply
просто представитель военкомат всё
heard everything, little brother, I asked for leave to go to
слышал братишечка я всё отпросился в
your Kursk region, well, in
вашу Курскую область ну меня вообще
short, the
короче
Kruchans told me: "Oh, sit in Crimea," well,
кручане сказали: "Ёх сиди в Крыму" ну да
well, damn, how do you mean sit in Crimea, on the
ну блин как это сиди в Крыму у нас
contrary, we didn't have enough, how do you mean sit in Crimea,
наоборот не хватало как это сиди в Крыму
I talked to your main leopard, leopard 11, the
я общался с вашим главным барсом барс 11
most important one there, who is he, you have a
самым главным там кто он у вас там дани
message for me, well,
мне послание
maybe you know, I'll tell you honestly,
ну может знаешь я тебе честно скажу у
we don't like Crimeans because we have
нас крымских не любят потому что у нас
special  some friends not me I'll
особенны какие-то друзья не я тебе я
explain to you look when our
тебе объясню смотри когда у нас началось
SVO started we were all like generally happy
СВО у нас все типа вообще были довольны
and everything was fine yeah because now in
и всё нормально да потому что там сейчас
short they'll capture Kyiv and everything like and
короче Киев захватят и всё типа
when Belgorod and Kursk started we had
а когда начали Белгород и Курск у нас
a few of everyone when they climbed uh in short into
немного всех когда полезли ээ короче в
Sudzha we were immediately asked the question:
Суджу у нас сразу поставили вопрос: а
why did they annex Crimea yes the
какого Крым присоединили да
Ukrainians in short are now climbing into the Kursk
украинцы короче лезут сейчас в Курскую
region and the Crimeans don't want to help
область а крымчане не хотят помогать у
us really like we have Khinshtein you know
нас реально типа у нас хнштейну знаешь
our governor Khinshtein to him in short on No I don't
губернатор наш Хинштейн ему короче на Не
know listen we have here I'll
не знаю слышишь у нас тут я тебе
tell you honestly I'll
расскажу вот честно вот тебе
tell you our tenth battalion Bars Crimea
расскажу наш десятый батальон Барс Крым
was rushing to you in the Kursk region we weren't
рвался к вам в Курскую область нас не
allowed in
пустили
how it broke away where it was breaking through and we weren't allowed
как оторвался куда он прорывался и не
we wanted to help you go there
пустил мы хотели вам помочь туда поехать
and weren't allowed to help people there we weren't
и не пустили людям помочь там нас не
allowed I'm answering you
пустили я тебе отвечаю
and are you a serviceman or are you just like a
а ты военнослужащий или ты просто типа
volunteer
доброволец
I'm a volunteer and why don't you go as a
я доброволец а что не пойдёшь
serviceman it's too
военнослужащим
late I've already won my own I mean it's too
уже поздно я уже свою отвоевал в смысле
late they take from us up to 60 years old well I don't understand
поздно до 60 лет берут у нас ну не понял
again from me  neighbor is 59 years old he went
ещё раз у меня соседу 59 лет он пошёл
like signed a contract
типа контракт подписал
[music] the
[музыка]
thing is that I'm already a retired military man
дело в том что я уже военный пенсионер
how old are you
сколько тебе лет
exactly 40 wait that is you are 40 years old
40 ровно подожди то есть ты тебе 40 лет
when in short Russia returned Crimea to itself you
когда короче Россия вернула Крым себе
were what is 30
тебе было сколько получается 30
well 30 years old now you are 40 my
ну 30 лет сейчас тебе 40 мой
classmate Sanya I
одноклассник Саня у меня вот 20 лет
went to serve for 20 years wait so you served in
пошёл служить подожди так ты служил в
Ukraine I
Украине
also served in Ukraine that is you in short
я ещё в Украине служил то есть ты короче
nav worked yes my classmate Then Russia
нав работал да мой однокла Потом Россия
took Crimea which we didn't need
взяла себе Крым который нам не был нужен
we could have come to Yalta anyway and
вот в Ялту мы и так могли приехать и
now you Wait you
теперь ты Подожди ты
worked for 10 years yes
работал 10 лет да
fought on the Etitovsky in short all these
воевал на этитовские короче все эти
jokes yes-yes yes and now in short my
приколы да-дада а теперь короче мой
classmate from Kursk Sanya Prokhorov
одноклассник из Курска Саня Прохоров
stupidly had his head chopped off with a drone
тупо ему башку шили дроном из-за того
because you are a retired military man in Crimea what are you
что ты военный пенсионер в Крыму вы что
Crimeans I still can't hear you
там крымчане я тебя всё равно не слышу
what are you shouting there everything you hear you
что ты там кричишь всё ты слышишь ты
in short what do
короче
you hear me what do you hear because we
что ты мне слышишь ты что потому что мы
annexed you for that  to
вас присоединили для того чтобы вас
help you get away and you
помочь вас отвпасти а вы Курскую область
don't want to defend Kursk region
не хотите защищать
idirol I wanted to go to Kursk come on come on come
идироле я хотел в Курск поехать давай
what's
давай приезжай приезжай что тут тут
free here in Kursk you can at They won't let us in
свободно в Курск можно при Нас не
there you go to Samkursk where
пускают туда заезжаешь в самкурск куда
[laughter]
[смех]
magic
волшебный
number they won't let us in they didn't let the Barsiks
номер не пускают не пускали барсики
hold on they won't let us in
держитесь нас не
like pitpska komen
пускают лайк питпска комен
hello where are you from polygraph
здравствуйте вы откуда полиграф
Polygraphich
Полиграфич
Sharikov we are from Russia from Russia I see I understood the
шариков мы с с России с России я вижу
police I see what
понял полицу вижу о чём общаетесь Шарик
you are talking about Sharik Sharikovich what are you
Шарикович что вы скажете шарик Шарикович
talking about
о чём общаетесь
what will you say let's talk we can
о чём скажете давайте поговорим можем
even talk about your cats let's talk
даже о ваших кошиках давайте поговорим
why is Russia at war with Ukraine
почему Россия воюет с Украиной
and what do you think I asked you that's
а как вы думаете я же вас и спросил
why to find out what you think well
поэтому чтобы узнать как вы думаете
usually Sharik Sharikovich told
ну обычно Шарик Шарикович рассказывал
how he crushed cats crushed crushed crushed well he
как он кошек давил давил давил давил ну
didn't crush enough that there are a
так не додавил что
lot of homeless cats left
кошек много осталось бездомных
Russia picks up
россия поднимает
takes and feeds why is it like
забирает и кормит почему
that with Sharikov with Sharikov how  how is
так у Шариковы у Шариковы как как
it what can I say
там что там можно сказать
everything is over words
всё закончились слова
yes no I'm thinking thinking thinking how to
да нет я вот думаю думаю думаю как
express myself correctly come on
правильно выразиться
tell me what's up and what's that
давай рассказывай что как дела а что у
you have drying right behind you right above your head a
тебя там сзади сушится прямо над головой
bunch of stuff yes
куча всего
there's a whole bunch of stuff I came home on vacation you
да там всего всего домой приехал в
know you're not the first
отпуск вот знаешь вот ты не первый
to ask and not the
спрашиваешь и не
first to come home on vacation washed my clothes
первый домой приехал в отпуск постирался
lady look why do you have it like this Why do you have a house
даме виду почему у тебя такой Почему у
that you have to
тебя дом что тебе приходится над головой
dry something above your head and what do you think
у себя сушить что-то а ты как думаешь
if I haven't been home for 4 years
если я 4 года дома не был
in the
на зоне сидел
maybe and so to speak slides sat
ну может быть и так сказать
a little I
посиживал немножко
understood well you have an imprint on your face and it
понял ну у тебя отпечаток на лице и
remained yes like that yes there are a lot of
остался да такой да много там знаешь
imprints and anger
отпечатков и злости
and God listen and what do you
и боже слушай а как ты
think why do people in America they
считаешь почему вот люди в Америке они
all look somehow with dull faces
все как-то выглядят с потухшими лицами
toothless I haven't
беззубые я что-то не
noticed something well do you believe you're the first to
замечал ну ты веришь ты первое
ask about this how do they look
спрашиваешь об этом как как они выглядят
I know I haven't even noticed
я знать я даже не замечал
I noticed you
я замечал
know in blues you know how girls
знаешь в голуки знаешь как это девчонки
age so
стареют так
quickly they're
быстро им
18 and if you look at them
18 а на них посмотришь
they're even 28  30 they sat about about for
им даже 28 30 они просидели про про за
e during these
э за эти
years under the bombing they are like And old
годы под бомбёжками они такие И старый
Stalin and how old are you by the way
Сталин а тебе сколько лет кстати
you look young by the way you
ну ты молодо выглядишь кстати ты
look about 27
выглядишь на 27
somewhere thank you thank you thank you thank you as
где-то дякую дякую дякую дякую как там у
you say thank you well
вас говорится дякую
and my brother said he says you what and and and my
ну и и брат сказал говорит ты что и и и
son and daughter say: "Daddy what are you they have
сын с дочкой говорит: "Папка ты что они
n't seen me for 2 years
меня 2 с по года не
years this vacation was not a
года этот отпуска не
nightmare now I came over there they are now
кошмар сейчас приехал вон они сейчас
sleeping and I'm in a madhouse it's going strong there's no
спят а у меня дурка прёт
sleep
прёт сна нет
somehow unusually
как-то необычно
quiet no shooting no bombing how did you get
тихо не стреляют не бомбит
to the war my
как на войну попал
wife was killed in
жену убили
eighteen my wife was killed in eighteen
восемнадцаты жену в восемнадцатом убили
where in Gorlovka well so where do you
где в Горловке ну так ты же сейчас где
live now you're not in Gorlovka now in Bashkiria
живёшь ты не в Горловке сейчас Башкирии
with your mother and father in the house so with your mother so
у матери с отцом в доме так у мате так а
where did you live in eighteen
где ты жил в восемнадцатом году
in Gorlovka on Leni on Leninka and how did you
в Горловке на Лени на Ленинке а как ты
get to Gorlovka
попал в Горловку
got married when
дженился когда
well I got married in sixteen that is you
ну я в шестнадцатом женился а то есть ты
in the sixteenth year I came to
в шестнадцатом году приехал в
occupied Gorlovka
оккупированную Горловку
not me in the sixteenth year she came to study
не я в шестнадцатом году она на учёбу
in Krasnodar we
приехала в Краснодар мы там
met there got married for what kind of study
познакомились женились на какую учёбу
how old was she she was
сколько ей лет было
18 years old she came to study
ей 18 лет было она приехала на учёбу
wait in the sixteenth year that's 10 years
подожди в шестнадцатом году это 10 лет
ago yes yes she was 18 and you were 40 oh 38 it was
назад да да ей 18 а тебе 40 ой 38 было
yes cool that is she is young
да прикольно то есть она молоденькая
eighteen years old and you
восемнадцатилетняя а ты
yes she was 20 years younger she
да на 20 лет она младше была она ей
needed her and
нужен был вот
I am an army man I am a handsome man I came with the
а я армейский я красавчик приехал я с
army then I was a handsome man yes you can't
армией был тогда красавчик да не
argue with your heart handsome you
поспоришь тебе сердечко красавчик ты
just know Apollo you know Miss Mister
прямо знаешь Аполлон знаешь мис мистер
Krasnodar
Краснодар
and what about you I am still a handsome man
а что у тебя я до сих пор красавчик
maybe you have a cool chest well
может у тебя грудак клёвый есть а ну
show it
покажи
flash it well then show it with them well like for
засвети ну так покажи сними ну как для
girls like what she
девчонок типа как она
looks like show it you have pumped up
выглядит покажи есть подкачанная
breasts
грудь
yeah what I have no need to
угу что у меня есть не надо мне
show me got it in short you are some
показывать понял короче ты какой-то
ordinary one who is deceiving there was no
обычный который обманываешь не было у
you didn't have an eighteen year old girl that's
тебя девчонки восемнадцатилетней не было
exactly what was there wasn't
вот именно что была не было
yeah and they shot her
угу и расстреляли её в восемнадцатом
in the throat in 1918 when she was digging potatoes
году в горло когда она картошку копала
wow where where they shot
вау где где расстреляли в восемнадцатом
her in 1918 while she was digging potatoes
году её как картошку копал
horror and what did they shoot her with
ужас а из чего расстреляли
from their guns on Well as an army you
из своих орудий на Ну как армейский ты
know it's from a grad from a pistol from an
же знаешь это из града из пистолета из
airplane what did they shoot with I was
самолёта из чего же стреляли
n't there I was in the army I'm
меня не было я на армии был я тебе
telling you I'm an army man RF
говорю я армейский РФ
so where were you in the army at that
так где ты был на армии в это
time I was earning money in Syria I understand then
время я зарабатывал в Сирии понял то
look you were in Syria an army man yeah and who
смотри ты был в Сирии армейский да а кто
told you that she was shot
тебе сказал что её расстреляли
her parent
её родитель
yeah and what did they shoot her with how could she have been shot by
угу а из чего её расстреляли как может
some Gorlovka
её расстреляли какие-то горловские
boys
пацаны
yeah with shrapnel and from a crater yeah what did they
угу осколками и с воронки да то чем чем
shoot with
расстреляли
I don't know what what when When did she
я не знаю чем что когда Когда у неё
When did she
Когда у неё
Look at me as her parents told me so and
Смотри мне как родители её сказали так и
so I look in 1918 there were
так я смотри восемнадцатом году там
maybe a few dead tell me uh in
может единицы было погибших скажи ээ в
what month  and what was her name now I'll
каком месяце и как её звали сейчас я
find it on the Internet or
найду в интернете или действительно так
was it really like that Alyonka Alyon Alyoshina Alyonka Alyonka yeah
было алёнка
Alyonka Gorlovka
алёшина алёнка угу алёна Горловка
yeah I ca
угу
n't find anything Alyoshina Alena Gorlovka
не находит ничего алёшина Алёна Горловка
not a single news item not a
ни одной новости нет
single one so
ни одно так
and did you have anything in Ukraine at least I'm
а у вас в Украине что-нибудь было хоть я
looking but I want to find news that
смотрю но я хочу найти новость чтобы
Alyoshina Alena from Gorlovka died no
Алёшина Алёна из Горловки погибла нет
such thing it seems
такого
and did you have anything it seems but
походу а у вас что-нибудь было походу а
about the children nothing but you
про детей нет а про каждого ребёнка ты
can find about each child look and if if
можешь найти вот смотри а если если если
if send me the address send me your address it
если скинька мне адрес адрес свой скинь
seems you
походу ты
No you have Internet yes it seems you
Нет у тебя интернет есть да походу ты
let me go to al na na angel alley
давай я на ал на на аллею ангела заеду
and you will look for each child
да и каждого ты ребёнка будешь искать
in short you
короче ты
Yes yes well when was that shelling well
Да да хорошо когда этот был обстрел
when did
ну когда погибла
your favorite die
твоя любимица
20 now now now
20 сейчас сейчас сейчас
tochem
точем
2per
2пер 21
February 21 eighteenth we buried her
февраля восемнадцатого года мы её
what year
какого года
eighteenth seventeenth
восемнадцатого семнадцатого
eighteenth
восемнадцатого восемнадцатого
so so I'm looking uh the list of shellings for
так так я смотрю ээ список обстрелов за
February  2018 in Gorlovka not a
февраль 2018 года в Горловке не
single shelling was recorded
зафиксировано ни одного обстрела
and you in Russian go to the chat also in Russian
а ты на русский зайди чат таж на русский
yes I'm on the site obserskayamisiya
да я на сайте обсерускаямисия
so you
так что ты
no I'm on the twenty first I'm on the twenty
нет я двадцать пер я двадцать
first of
пер
February they buried I couldn't come I
февраля они похоронили я не смог
couldn't come I was
приехать я не смог
busy I was busy in February I did
приехать я занятый был я в феврале был
n't come I came later yes yes
занят я не приехал я позже приехал да да
I immediately took over
я сразу
thwarted the PMC I
сорвал ЧВК я
thwarted and came and entered yes in short you So
сорвал и приехал и поступил да короче ты
you
Так и ты
go and dug up potatoes in February
идёшь картошку в феврале накопала
subscribe to my Instagram I don't know why
підпишись на мій Instagram я не знаю для
you do it why else are you there to
чого це тобі для чго ще тобі там
watch on Face but for you it's one or
дивитись на Face але для тебе це оди або
three
три
clicks you support me and I will say:
клика підтримаєш мене и я буду казати:
"Wow I have a bunch of followers and I
"Вау в мене там купа фоловерів и в мене
will be cool
буде класний
tune in to my Instagram pop Andriy"
настроись на мій Instagram попик Андрій"
so let me wait for you
отак давай я тебя очекаю